Kien Hoang

Anaheim, California, United States

kien.dv2012@gmail.com

(949) 609-9578

linkedin.com/in/kien-hoang-165977139

Summary

I have 4 years experiences in sales, operation, strategic planning and management. In addition, I have bachelor's degree in Hospitality and Tourism. I have a strong experience in customer service. A strong background in customer service helps me to assist the most enjoyable experience. I can find my career highlight below

Experience



District Manager

Securitas Security Services USA, Inc.

Dec 2020 - Dec 2021 (1 year 1 month)

Oversee and manage more than 30 accounts in Orange County. Supervising approximately 100 employees daily. The goal is to handle any issue from the client as well as the employees to not only build a strong relationship with employee, lowering retention rate but to ensure quality of services, customer satisfaction.

- -Coaches, trains, and develops many key positions in the field such as account managers, supervisors, scheduler. Proven by helping more than 5 employee promoted this year.
- -Playing an HR role to create a safety environment, following up to standard of OSHA compliance, hosting training weekly basis for the employees. Assisting with HR to interview new hire and orientation.
- -Ensures profitable operations with full profit and loss accountability by analyze operational and financial indicators. Total revenue is up by %10.5 YTD.

Assistant Branch Manager

Enterprise

May 2018 - Nov 2020 (2 years 7 months)

Supervised branch operations for multiple cornerstone locations, 1200+ cars

- -Minimized expenses by monitoring controllable and cutting costs
- -Instilled strong sales culture resulting revenue increase of \$1.50/car over a fleet of 1200 cars
- -Led region and ranked #1 in branch overall performance in September 2019
- -Promoted a fun and competitive work environment through building team morale and creative sales competitions



GUEST SERVICE AGENT

Le Méridien Hotels & Resorts

Jan 2018 - May 2018 (5 months)

Interacted with guests and handled guest's daily issues

- -Developed sales technique to achieve the hotel business target
- -Communicated with other departments (Housekeeping, Security, Food& Beverage, etc..) to ensure the VIP guests rooms meet its standard

-Ensured all paperwork was in order and correctly submitted to Manager on Duty and Financial department

Education



Web Developer 2022 - Present UCI Bootcamp

Kaplan Professional

Hospitality and Management

Murdoch University

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE, Hospitality & Tourism Management and Management